question_data = [
    {"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Japanese Anime &amp; Manga","question":"No Game No Life first aired in 2014.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"New Haven is the capital city of the state of Connecticut in the United States.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Film","question":"The 2010 film &quot;The Social Network&quot; is a biographical drama film about MySpace founder Tom Anderson.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Mythology","question":"According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Video Games","question":"Solid Snake is actually a clone from the DNA of Big Boss in the Metal Gear Solid series&#039; history.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Entertainment: Books","question":"The Harry Potter series of books, combined, are over 1,000,000 words in length.","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"Pluto is a planet.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Geography","question":"Hungary is the only country in the world beginning with H.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"Animals","question":"A bear does NOT defecate during hibernation. ","correct_answer":"True","incorrect_answers":["False"]},{"type":"boolean","difficulty":"easy","category":"General Knowledge","question":"In architecture, a &quot;pecklesteiner&quot; is a set of doors that overlap each other when closed, and can be locked through a single keyhole.","correct_answer":"False","incorrect_answers":["True"]}
    ]